dymm.com 2013-11-27

# 

DYMM has adopted this privacy policy in order to ensure users of our commitment and dedication to privacy. The following privacy guidelines apply to the website "DYMM.com" (Site). DYMM respects your right to privacy. We invite you to visit our site to search or browse the site without revealing who you are or registering with us. However, if you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need, it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will endeavor to respect your wishes.

**Registration  
**  
Registration is not required to gain access to the Site. However, there are sections of the web site which do require registration at the time of purchase.

Collection of IP addresses and the use of "Cookies"

When you visit our Site, some information such as your Internet protocol address, Internet service provider, operating system, the Site from which you arrived, and the time and date of your visit may be collected automatically as part of the software operation of this Site. This intake of information is not personally identifiable. DYMM uses this information solely for internal marketing purposes, for example, to see what pages are most frequently visited in order to improve the Site. After it is used for internal marketing purposes, this information is discarded.

We also collect information through the use of a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a small file that a web site can send to your browser, which is then stored on your system by your browser. The use of cookie technology on DYMM.com is solely for internal marketing purposes. If you are uncomfortable accepting cookies from our Site or any other, you can set your browser to notify you when a Site attempts to send you a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide for yourself whether or not to accept the cookie. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies.

**Personal Information  
**  
Any time DYMM collects information that you voluntarily submit, it is DYMM' intent to inform you of why this information is being requested and how it is going to be used. We may collect personal information from you including phone, electronic mail address, and other information you choose to provide at various times, for example, when you complete an online form or request. DYMM uses the personal information we collect online to process your requests, inform you of opportunities that we believe you might find interesting, and to understand your needs so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. DYMM intends to protect and secure the personal information that you submit to this Site. DYMM will not sell, distribute, or give your personal information to any third party without your knowledge and consent. DYMM shall not be liable for any personal information that you submit to external vendors or to any web site linked to this Site.

**Children's usage of the Site  
**  
This Site is intended for adult use only. It is not intended for children, and we ask that minors not submit any personal information to us. Certain sections of this website contain adult images. This site is not suitable for children.

**Nature of Data on the Internet  
**  
It is DYMM' intent to guard any personal information that you submit to us, and DYMM will continue to take steps to maintain the security of this Site. However, as a multi-national corporation, the data we collect from you may be internationally distributed throughout DYMM and the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. Therefore, in submitting personal information to the Site, you assume the risk of a third party obtaining that information.
